I worked all days of the week
Since I was still new to everything
Anxiety would take over me
I get broken sometimes
I worked all days of the week
Even if it’s tough, I could only try harder everyday
But once Friday ends it’ll all be fine
I will go and meet my hero on the weekend
No, there is no way, I can’t even stand up
I want to change myself, so I will go today
It doesn't always work out
There are tough times that make you want to cry
When that happens
I just want to meet the hero that rises up before anyone
Although it’s painful and it hurts, I still ran
I don’t know if I will be rewarded
But for now, I will not be beaten
With my hero and myself
Even tomorrow
All days of the week, I go to school
Keeping up with what my friends talk about is actually quite tough for me
What I really like is not yesterday’s TV show
All days of the week, I go to school
I actually don’t even know Shibuya nor Harajuku
But once Friday ends it’ll all be fine
I will go and meet my hero on the weekend
No, there is no way, I can’t even wipe my tears
I want to change myself, so I will go today
I may be laughed by other people for getting anxious over a tiny thing
Without even smiling, he will show me
My hero will teach me, how to run
Although it’s painful and it hurts, I still ran
I don’t know if tomorrow will be any different
But for now, I will not be beaten
With my hero and myself
Even tomorrow
It doesn't always work out
There are tough times that make you want to cry
When that happens
I just want to meet the hero that rises up before anyone
Although it’s painful and it hurts, I still ran
I don’t know if I will be rewarded
But for now, I will not be beaten
With my hero and myself
Even tomorrow
Work, relationships, and education
None of these can be omitted
Just think it’s for your future
Crying is not a bad thing
Encourage yourself from yesterday
And just run earnestly today
He will teach me how to run again
With my hero and myself
Even tomorrow